{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430da1"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-career-advice-for-a-software-developer-to-earn-a-higher-salary?-", 
    "answer" : "Alex Rogachevsky, Lifetime programmer, startup CTOAnswered 4 years ago · Author has 636 answers and 4.3M answer viewsWhat is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary? Alex Rogachevsky Solve a problem. A business one - that created the need for the software you are developing. Software is such a complex product (like cars and houses), it requires a team of engineers. Employers pigeonhole developers into little specializations. You can happily stay a sniper, machine gunner, or radio operator in your squad arrangement. You can even go to the officer’s academy (business school) to be promoted through official channels. But you need to try it first: comprehending the whole battle and rising above the specialist rank. At least in your mind. You don’t have to write the entire system’s code to do that. Just look at the big picture, identify problems not directly related to you, raise them, and help your teammates to solve them. Solve some yourself - something outside your special Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.432+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is the best career advice for a software developer to earn a higher salary? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430da3"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Tia-Carrere-alive?-", 
    "answer" : "Thirty seconds on Google or IMDB will answer this question for you, and you won’t have to sort through a bunch of different answers. In this case it’ll be faster and more direct to just look up the info…Quora is just a waste of time. 4", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.716+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is Tia Carrere alive? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430da5"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-one-make-carrer-in-meme-making?-", 
    "answer" : "Questions Sumit Pandey", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.719+0000"), 
    "question" : "How can one make carrer in meme making? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430da7"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-carrers-growth-foe-for-technical-branch-in-AFCAT?-", 
    "answer" : "Alpingi, writing everything on AFCAT at techmario.comAnswered 3 years ago · Author has 119 answers and 1.6M answer viewsWhat is the eligibility criteria for AFCAT non technical? Alpingi", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.722+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is the carrers growth foe for technical branch in AFCAT? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430da9"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-Marketing-Management-carrers?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Tricia Labrie Katy Harlow", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.736+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are Marketing Management carrers? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dab"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Computer-sciencie-one-of-the-best-carrers?-", 
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Jimmy Kuo 1", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.740+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is Computer sciencie one of the best carrers? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dad"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-carrer-options-after-bsc-computer-science?-", 
    "answer" : "Questions Barkha Barkat", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.744+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the best carrer options after bsc computer science? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430daf"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Does-VFX-carrer-has-a-scope-or-future-in-India?-", 
    "answer" : "Yes, it does. In the recent past, several Hollywood studios and companies from the west have started investing in India. And Indian VFX studios, too, are flourishing with each passing year. A lot of people find it hard to believe, but the visual effects for some of the biggest blockbusters (300: Rise of an Empire, Godzilla, Maleficent, The Hunger Games, Jupiter Ascending and Pixels) were in fact done here in India. Since it is a market that is known to churn out high-quality VFX work in quick time, India has become the outsourcing hub when it comes to visual effects work for films, television shows, web series and other projects. India-based films and series, too, require heavy VFX inputs and they prefer getting them done from domestic studios and agencies. As an aspiring VFX professional, t Continue Reading Yes, it does. In the recent past, several Hollywood studios and companies from the west have started investing in India. And Indian VFX studios, too, are flourishing with each passing year. A lot of people find it hard to believe, but the visual effects for some of the biggest blockbusters (300: Rise of an Empire, Godzilla, Maleficent, The Hunger Games, Jupiter Ascending and Pixels) were in fact done here in India. Since it is a market that is known to churn out high-quality VFX work in quick time, India has become the outsourcing hub when it comes to visual effects work for films, television shows, web series and other projects. India-based films and series, too, require heavy VFX inputs and they prefer getting them done from domestic studios and agencies. As an aspiring VFX professional, t Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.748+0000"), 
    "question" : "Does VFX carrer has a scope or future in India? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430db1"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-future-on-Salesforce?-", 
    "answer" : "Future of Salesforce will be bright and keen, it will continue to grow further and reaches new heights. First thing is Salesforce CRM is market leader in CRM domain and generating huge revenue as well as employment and equal pay. It's a world's top 10 company with great values and vision and global work culture (recently ranked by Forbes top 10 companies to work in 2019). How can i become a salesforce engineer? If you want to get a job on Salesforce technology, then you need to learn that subject first then there will be an exam called Salesforce Certification. Every person who wants to enter into salesforce must and should write Salesforce certification exam and pass it, then you will get a ID number. So and so person passed Salesforce exam and his/her ID is xxxxx. like that you will get. T Continue Reading Future of Salesforce will be bright and keen, it will continue to grow further and reaches new heights. First thing is Salesforce CRM is market leader in CRM domain and generating huge revenue as well as employment and equal pay. It's a world's top 10 company with great values and vision and global work culture (recently ranked by Forbes top 10 companies to work in 2019). How can i become a salesforce engineer? If you want to get a job on Salesforce technology, then you need to learn that subject first then there will be an exam called Salesforce Certification. Every person who wants to enter into salesforce must and should write Salesforce certification exam and pass it, then you will get a ID number. So and so person passed Salesforce exam and his/her ID is xxxxx. like that you will get. T Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.751+0000"), 
    "question" : "How is the future on Salesforce? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430db3"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-MBA-after-CS-with-BBA-is-a-good-carrer-option?-", 
    "answer" : "Yes, MBA is definitely a good career option after BBA with CS. Higher degree in the similar field will give you a more varied knowledge along with practical skills provided in the course. If you are looking for an MBA college in Rajasthan, you can apply with Sir Padampat Singhania University in Udaipur. SPSU is established by J. K. Cement Ltd. and provides quality education and practical learning environment to the students. SPSU provides dual specialization along with practical approach being followed in almost every aspect of education which is very essential for the MBA students. SPSU has a very strong industrial network and so the students get an exclusive opportunity of paid internships and final placements in top companies of India and abroad at high salary packages. Students get exc Continue Reading Yes, MBA is definitely a good career option after BBA with CS. Higher degree in the similar field will give you a more varied knowledge along with practical skills provided in the course. If you are looking for an MBA college in Rajasthan, you can apply with Sir Padampat Singhania University in Udaipur. SPSU is established by J. K. Cement Ltd. and provides quality education and practical learning environment to the students. SPSU provides dual specialization along with practical approach being followed in almost every aspect of education which is very essential for the MBA students. SPSU has a very strong industrial network and so the students get an exclusive opportunity of paid internships and final placements in top companies of India and abroad at high salary packages. Students get exc Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.755+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is MBA after CS with BBA is a good carrer option? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430db5"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-digital-marekting-has-carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.764+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is digital marekting has carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430db7"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-must-choose-lawyer-as-my-carrer-or-business-as-my-carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "Uthirapathy Kadirvelayudham", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.767+0000"), 
    "question" : "Should I must choose lawyer as my carrer or business as my carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430db9"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-start-my-carrer-as-medical-rep-in-pharma-at-age-of-29?-", 
    "answer" : "It is very difficulty to get a job of Medical Representative at the age of 29 in any renowned pharmaceutical company. Because most of the leading companies put maximum age limit upto 26 years. However, you can start your career and can get opportunity in newer companies. You join there and do hard work. You can make your mark in pharma industry and will be noticed by good companies by dint of your hard work. The pharma industry always appreciate the hard workers and result oriented persons. With in one or two years , you can get opportunity to work in the topmost companies where sky is the only limit. All the best….", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.770+0000"), 
    "question" : "Can I start my carrer as medical rep in pharma at age of 29? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dbb"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-carrer-opportunities-after-pursuing-honours-in-English?-", 
    "answer" : "One may choose from a range of careers like academics, journalism, advertising, and content writing. JOB OPPORTUNITIES FOR LITERATURE STUDENTS Media and JournalismPublishing industryTeaching & researchAdvertising & MarketingHR/ Administration jobs in public and private sectorHospitality industryTranslatorsTechnical WritersContent DevelopersCivil ServicesTop colleges for Fine Arts: Lovely Professional University, Jalandhar Goenka College of Commerce and Business Administration - Kolkata K J Somaiya College of Arts & Commerce ‒ Mumbai Mithibai College - Mumbai Delhi College of Arts & Commerce (DCAC) - Delhi Good Luck", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.774+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the carrer opportunities after pursuing honours in English? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dbd"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-agricultural-engineering-is-used-as-Carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "Deepak Pasupuleti Since I am an agricultural engineer I can answer your question. See you have various career options depending on the college you choose to study. If you study in a private collage-like me you end up getting offers from mostly private-owned companies because my college is not an ICAR recognized one Come to the govt colleges there are vide range of options you can choose and mostly you will definitely have field experience more compared to me and you can give ICAR exam only if you are from ICAR recognized college since most of the govt colleges are recognized you are can easily give many govt related exams are there are 100% chances of selecting you. Here are career options for private colleges >Private irrigation companies (NETAFIM, SIFLON, M&M IRRIGATION, JAIN, etc) >Field sales for various far Continue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.781+0000"), 
    "question" : "How is agricultural engineering is used as Carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dbf"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Could-biking-be-pursued-as-a-carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.785+0000"), 
    "question" : "Could biking be pursued as a carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dc1"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-carrer-oppurtunities-after-bsc-and-msc-in-physics?-", 
    "answer" : "Physics Graduates can find ample career openings both in public as well as private sector enterprises. They can apply for all government jobs that insight graduation as thebasic Qualification. One can find various opprotunities in governmental organisation like DRDO, VSSC, ISRO, SSPL etc Can also recruited in space research centers and in research laboratories. The Following list shows some of the common job types and Employment areas for Physics graduate: Job Types: Lab Supervisor Researcher Technician Teacher Scientist Consulting Physicist Research Associate Senior Physicist Assistant Scientist Radiation Oncologist Radiolist Professor Main Employment Areas: Research Insititutes Laboratories and Insititutes Educational Insititutes Agriculatural Research services Hospitals Power Generating Companies Aviation Indus Continue Reading Physics Graduates can find ample career openings both in public as well as private sector enterprises. They can apply for all government jobs that insight graduation as thebasic Qualification. One can find various opprotunities in governmental organisation like DRDO, VSSC, ISRO, SSPL etc Can also recruited in space research centers and in research laboratories. The Following list shows some of the common job types and Employment areas for Physics graduate: Job Types: Lab Supervisor Researcher Technician Teacher Scientist Consulting Physicist Research Associate Senior Physicist Assistant Scientist Radiation Oncologist Radiolist Professor Main Employment Areas: Research Insititutes Laboratories and Insititutes Educational Insititutes Agriculatural Research services Hospitals Power Generating Companies Aviation Indus Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.788+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are the carrer oppurtunities after bsc and msc in physics? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dc3"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-do-BBA-+-LLB?-", 
    "answer" : "Hi After the liberalization of India’s economy there is a huge demand for highly skilled lawyers. If you want to pursue your career in law after 12th standard then you can go for some integrated degree like BBA + LL.b hons. BBA + LL.b Hons. : Graduates may opt for legal practice, where management foundation will groom aspiring lawyers for the corporate sector. Some of the career prospects of BBA LLB hons are : You can appear for Civil and Judicial services in your respective States, IAS Services, JAGS, services in Army, Corporate Lawyer, Legal Advisors in MNC’s and Company’s, Legal Processing outsourcing, Practice in Criminal, Civil or Income Tax as an advocate. It will be advisable if you do your degree from a well known university and that provides prime placement opportunity, outstanding expo Continue Reading Hi After the liberalization of India’s economy there is a huge demand for highly skilled lawyers. If you want to pursue your career in law after 12th standard then you can go for some integrated degree like BBA + LL.b hons. BBA + LL.b Hons. : Graduates may opt for legal practice, where management foundation will groom aspiring lawyers for the corporate sector. Some of the career prospects of BBA LLB hons are : You can appear for Civil and Judicial services in your respective States, IAS Services, JAGS, services in Army, Corporate Lawyer, Legal Advisors in MNC’s and Company’s, Legal Processing outsourcing, Practice in Criminal, Civil or Income Tax as an advocate. It will be advisable if you do your degree from a well known university and that provides prime placement opportunity, outstanding expo Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.796+0000"), 
    "question" : "Can I do BBA + LLB? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dc5"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-carrers-in-CS?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.800+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are carrers in CS? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dc7"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-carrer-should-I-choose-if-am-not-interested-in-anything-and-is-aimless?-", 
    "answer" : "Relax! You are experiencing something which is very common. Most people won’t discuss about this, because they think it is ‘unethical’ to talk about. Later they choose a career which eventually kill their will to do anything. Never do that! Atleast, you are considering to choose a career. I really appreciate that! So, now that you have asked this question, I guess you might already have something in your mind as a career option, if not, then its fine. Just ask yourself this question, “What do I like to do?”. Your answer might be one of these, if not, then mention in the comment. CookingPlaying a music instrumentRiding motorcycleSportsMaking videosPhotographyPlaying gamesComedyMagicImpressions of celebritiesSinging Ever heard of PewDiePie ? If you haven't, because of some weird reason, then be sure to check him out. He is the most subscribed Youtuber, and made his career just by playing games. Believe me, there are so many successful people who made their career out of things you cannot imagine. So, choose a career based on something you’re really good at and like doing it. But, always remember the most important thing is, ‘you will have to work really hard to achieve success and be the best’. All the best and have a great life ahead! Follow me for more career related posts. Be sure to check out CybrHome - Explore The Internet for more career suggestions and options.", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.804+0000"), 
    "question" : "What carrer should I choose if am not interested in anything and is aimless? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dc9"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-carrer-options-after-Masters-in-Economics-other-than-Research?-", 
    "answer" : "DSE Entrance  Abhishek Dwivedi", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.812+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are carrer options after Masters in Economics other than Research? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430de0"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-one-can-become-millionaire-by-pursuing-carrer-in-tourism?-", 
    "answer" : "Questions Shoba Lal", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.915+0000"), 
    "question" : "How one can become millionaire by pursuing carrer in tourism? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430de2"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Do-INTPs-fare-well-in-medical-carrers?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.920+0000"), 
    "question" : "Do INTPs fare well in medical carrers? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430de4"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-do-you-think-of-Tia-Carrere?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.924+0000"), 
    "question" : "What do you think of Tia Carrere? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430de6"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/WHICH-are-the-best-CARRER-PAYMENT?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.926+0000"), 
    "question" : "WHICH are the best CARRER PAYMENT? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430de8"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Chartered-Accountancy-a-good-profession?-", 
    "answer" : "Zeal Karwa Chartered Accountants will always have bright future. There are many reasons which I have observed, personally. I will give you my example: I cleared my Chartered Accountancy in 2012, I started my career with Indirect Tax, then I moved in Investment Banking that is Hedge Funds and Mutual Funds, then I moved in Project Financing, Financial Modelling, Valuation and Acccounts Closing. This is possible just because of base of Chartered Accountant. The Chartered Accountant Course makes the base so strong that it enables student to go in any field which he likes without much struggle. So I find the Future of CA is very Bright and I am really proud of being CA. First of all, the syllabus of Chartered Accountant is so vast that helps CA to work in any field of Accounts, Taxes and Finances. For exampleContinue Reading Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.930+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is Chartered Accountancy a good profession? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dea"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-computer-science-engineering-is-right-carrer-option-or-not?-", 
    "answer" : "It matters only the fact that if you are: . . . If you are passionate about it or not .. .. so the cross question arises to you ARE YOU INTEReSTED IN COMPUTER SCIENCE ENGINEERING OR NOT?????????????? . . . Are your parents are forcing you to?? or do you want something else?? ……….enough of dots I’ll suggest you to go through your conscience or your spiritual being and ask that question same to yourself???: write journals that gonna help a lot a speaking fluent english.ask yourselfbe serious not worried like you keep thinking and stuff.never procrastinatefocus on every topichave a planstay awesome", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.937+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is computer science engineering is right carrer option or not? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dec"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-acturial-science-good-carrer-option-for-commerce-student?-", 
    "answer" : "Sukhvir Singh", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.941+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is acturial science good carrer option for commerce student? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430dee"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-carrer-in-physiotherapy-worth-it?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.945+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is a carrer in physiotherapy worth it? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430df0"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-ludicrous-to-try-learning-to-code-at-age-36-in-hopes-of-a-carrer-change?-", 
    "answer" : "No, it is not ludicrous. I started when I was 10 years older than you. However, you must evaluate the time you have available carefully, as you likely have other obligations and responsibilities at this point in life, such as family and work. Getting started is one thing, seeing things through to an intermediate level is another. There are many excellent ways to start, Learn to code and help nonprofits (freecodecamp dot com) is a good place to start, as is any of the online tutorials available at W3 Schools, codecademy, Khan Academy’s introduction to programming tutorials, Learn TreeHouse, and CodeSchool. You can find a good infographic regarding what language to start with at Carl Cheo’s website Which Programming Language Should I Learn First? [Infographic]. If nothing else, it will give you Continue Reading No, it is not ludicrous. I started when I was 10 years older than you. However, you must evaluate the time you have available carefully, as you likely have other obligations and responsibilities at this point in life, such as family and work. Getting started is one thing, seeing things through to an intermediate level is another. There are many excellent ways to start, Learn to code and help nonprofits (freecodecamp dot com) is a good place to start, as is any of the online tutorials available at W3 Schools, codecademy, Khan Academy’s introduction to programming tutorials, Learn TreeHouse, and CodeSchool. You can find a good infographic regarding what language to start with at Carl Cheo’s website Which Programming Language Should I Learn First? [Infographic]. If nothing else, it will give you Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.949+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is it ludicrous to try learning to code at age 36 in hopes of a carrer change? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430df2"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-different-carrer-choices-after-doing-btech?-", 
    "answer" : "There are several career choices and job opportunities if you are an Engineering Graduate. Some of the most common career options are: Further studies: Like M.Tech, MBA, or even Ph.D.Engineer in PSUs like BHEL, BEL, NTPC, ONGC, SAIL, IOCL, GAIL, and etc.Engineer or Scientist in DRDO, ISRO, and BARC.Engineer in Indian Railways.Executive Engineer or Associate Engineer in Private Sectors.You can start your own Business or Start-up if you have the required skills and sufficient capital.An IT freelancer.A Commissioned Officer in Indian Armed Force and Indian Defence forces like Assistant Commandant, Lieutenant, Flying Officer and etc. in Technical departments.A technical graduate teacher.Many other government services like Police and Ministry.These are some of the best career options you may cho Continue Reading There are several career choices and job opportunities if you are an Engineering Graduate. Some of the most common career options are: Further studies: Like M.Tech, MBA, or even Ph.D.Engineer in PSUs like BHEL, BEL, NTPC, ONGC, SAIL, IOCL, GAIL, and etc.Engineer or Scientist in DRDO, ISRO, and BARC.Engineer in Indian Railways.Executive Engineer or Associate Engineer in Private Sectors.You can start your own Business or Start-up if you have the required skills and sufficient capital.An IT freelancer.A Commissioned Officer in Indian Armed Force and Indian Defence forces like Assistant Commandant, Lieutenant, Flying Officer and etc. in Technical departments.A technical graduate teacher.Many other government services like Police and Ministry.These are some of the best career options you may cho Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.956+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are different carrer choices after doing btech? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430df4"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-i-start-my-carrer-in-cyber-security?-", 
    "answer" : "The absolute best way is to join the us air force. If you can, make sure you get an afsc (air force job) that has to do with computers and/or intelligence because it will just boost your experience. Some examples include:  Client Systems (3D1X1) Operations Intelligence Specialist (1N0X1) Network Intelligence Analyst Specialist (1N4X1) Cyber Surety (3D0X3) Cyber Systems Operations (3D0X2) Computer Systems Programming (3C0X2) Cyber Transport (3D1X2) Geospatial Intelligence (1N1X1)  While you are in your 4 or 6 year enlistment, work on your bachelors degree in something like Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or Computer Engineering. Many accredited schools offer these degrees online. Make sure you go to a REAL school, not one of those Kaplan/DeVry/University of Phoenix fake s Continue Reading The absolute best way is to join the us air force. If you can, make sure you get an afsc (air force job) that has to do with computers and/or intelligence because it will just boost your experience. Some examples include:  Client Systems (3D1X1) Operations Intelligence Specialist (1N0X1) Network Intelligence Analyst Specialist (1N4X1) Cyber Surety (3D0X3) Cyber Systems Operations (3D0X2) Computer Systems Programming (3C0X2) Cyber Transport (3D1X2) Geospatial Intelligence (1N1X1)  While you are in your 4 or 6 year enlistment, work on your bachelors degree in something like Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or Computer Engineering. Many accredited schools offer these degrees online. Make sure you go to a REAL school, not one of those Kaplan/DeVry/University of Phoenix fake s Continue Reading", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.962+0000"), 
    "question" : "How can i start my carrer in cyber security? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6754ed0dadcccc430df6"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-carrer-in-Tech-support-a-good-idea?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:28.970+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is a carrer in Tech support a good idea? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e19"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-HTML-and-CSS-good-for-testing-carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "Steve Mark", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.131+0000"), 
    "question" : "Is HTML and CSS good for testing carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e1b"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-are-the-carrer-opportunities-for-a-fresher-in-Commvault-systems-India?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.135+0000"), 
    "question" : "How are the carrer opportunities for a fresher in Commvault systems India? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e1d"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Carrer-option-at-policybazzar-is-good-or-not?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.138+0000"), 
    "question" : "Carrer option at policybazzar is good or not? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e1f"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-carrer-growth-in-Mindtree-as-dot-net-developer?-", 
    "answer" : "It depends on how you take the upcoming opportunities. If you love coding - you will be more than satisfied. Unlike other companies, projects are very challenging ( be it development from scratch or maintenance). You have to work hard and spend your whole day coding. Every single person in a project plays a different role. So you have to work on a module alone and you will learn innumerous things in this process. Moreover, you will not be on bench for much time. Once you get released from any project, many upcoming projects await you. You will be recognised if you have talent in you. You will love everything here (project, work environment, people). At the end what matters is your hardwork and dedication. All the best for your career ! :)", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.142+0000"), 
    "question" : "How is the carrer growth in Mindtree as dot net developer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e21"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-carrer-in-psychology-and-after-which-specific-degree?-", 
    "answer" : "Gyan Do Amit", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.146+0000"), 
    "question" : "What are carrer in psychology and after which specific degree? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e23"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-reason-for-selecting-CA-as-a-carrer?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.149+0000"), 
    "question" : "What is the reason for selecting CA as a carrer? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
{ 
    "_id" : ObjectId("602d6755ed0dadcccc430e25"), 
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-about-marine-engineering-as-a-carrer-option?-", 
    "answer" : "", 
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-17T18:58:29.152+0000"), 
    "question" : "How about marine engineering as a carrer option? ", 
    "source" : "Quora"
}
